Penny?
(Penny:)It was a letter explaining that your dad
wasn't who he said he was.
(Penny:)Eventually his other life caught up to him...
(Penny:)...and the only way to keep
you and your mom safe was to leave.
(Sheldon:)I would like to change mine.
(Sheldon:)The pirate's name was Peg-Leg Antoine.
(Sheldon:)Now it's completely different from Goonies.
- No, it's not.
- Don't.
(Leonard:)Okay, my turn.
(Leonard:)Your dad wrote about how family
is the most important thing...
(Leonard:)...and that you should never
throw it away like he did.
(Howard:)Hmm.
Bernadette?
In the envelope was a picture of your dad
holding you the day you were born.
(Bernadette:)On the back he wrote,
"Howard, my son, my greatest gift."